Guide to the Carl Van Vechten Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Printed Material, 1871-1986; Series V; 30.0; 32 boxes + 2 art, 2 broadsides, 1 broadside oversize
  - Non-Van Vechten/Marinoff Printed Material
    - Periodicals and Serials
      - Time
        - 1950 March 6 (Box 285, Folder 3012)
        - 1950 November 13 (Box 285, Folder 3013)
        - 1950 November 20 (Box 285, Folder 3014)
      - Tricolor, 1944 July (Box 285, Folder 3015)
      - The University of Tennessee Record, 1954 January (Box 285, Folder 3016)
      - Vogue
        - 1938 January 1 (Box 301, Folder 3160)
        - 1941 June 15 (Box 301, Folder 3161)
        - 1949 December (Box 301, Folder 3162)
      - Wagner Literary Magazine
        - 1960 (Box 286, Folder 3017)
        - 1962 (Box 286, Folder 3018)
      - Weekend Reporter, 1948 April 16 (Box 286, Folder 3019)
      - Yale Literary Magazine, 1958 December (Box 286, Folder 3020)
      - Yale University Faculty Handbook, 1963 July 1 (Box 286, Folder 3021)
      - Yale University Library Gazette
        - 1948 January (Box 286, Folder 3022)
        - 1948 July (Box 286, Folder 3023)
        - 1950 April (Box 286, Folder 3024)
        - 1953 October (Box 286, Folder 3025)
        - 1954 January (Box 286, Folder 3026)
        - 1954 April (Box 286, Folder 3027)
        - 1954 July (Box 286, Folder 3028)
        - 1955 January (Box 286, Folder 3029)
        - 1955 July (Box 286, Folder 3030)
        - 1957 July (Box 286, Folder 3031)
        - 1959 April (Box 286, Folder 3032)
        - 1959 July (Box 286, Folder 3033)
        - 1963 July (Box 286, Folder 3034)
      - Yale University Student Directory, 1952 November 1 (Box 286, Folder 3035)
      - Yale University Telephone Directory
        - 1951 November (Box 286, Folder 3036)
        - 1952 November (Box 286, Folder 3037)
    - Performance and Event Programs
      Includes handbills and flyers
      - Dance
        - Alicia Markova and Anton Dolin, 1949-1951, undated (Box 288, Folder 3049)
        - The American Ballet, 1935-1942, undated (Box 288, Folder 3050)
        - American Ballet Theatre, 1960, undated (Box 288, Folder 3051)
        - Argentina, 1929, 1939, undated (Box 288, Folder 3052)
        - Ballet Caravan, 1937 (Box 288, Folder 3053)
        - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo (Blum and de Basil), undated (Box 288, Folder 3054)
        - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo (de Basil) (Box 288, Folder 3055-3056)
        - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo (Denham), 1947–1948 (Box 289, Folder 3057)
        - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo (Massine), 1938–1941 (Box 289, Folder 3058-3059)
        - Ballet Society, 1946–1947 (Box 289, Folder 3060)
        - Ballet Theatre, 1940–1955 (Box 290, Folder 3061-3063)
        - Ballets de l'Opera de Paris, 1948 (Box 291, Folder 3064)
        - Les Ballets de Paris, 1949 (Box 291, Folder 3065)
        - Bolshoi Ballet, 1959, undated (Box 291, Folder 3066)
        - Folies-Bergère, 1930 (Box 291, Folder 3067)
        - Grand Ballet de Monte-Carlo, 1949 (Box 291, Folder 3068)
        - Hartford Festival, 1936 (Box 291, Folder 3069)
        - Imperial Russian Ballet and Orchestra, 1910 (Box 291, Folder 3070)
        - Inbal Dance Theatre of Israel, 1958 (Box 291, Folder 3071)
        - The Lotos Club Tribute to the Ballet, undated (Box 291, Folder 3072)
        - Martha Graham and Her Dance Company, 1960 (Box 291, Folder 3073)
        - Moiseyev Dance Company, 1958 (Box 291, Folder 3074)
        - Mumaw, undated (Box 291, Folder 3075)
        - New York City Ballet, 1949–1965 (Box 292, Folder 3076-3078)
        - Philadelphia Ballet Company, 1937 (Box 293, Folder 3079)
        - Ram Gopal and His Hindu Ballet, 1948 (Box 293, Folder 3080)
        - The Royal Ballet (formerly the Sadler's Wells Ballet), 1957, 1960 (Box 293, Folder 3081)
        - Royal Danish Ballet, 1956 (Box 293, Folder 3082)
        - Sadler's Wells Ballet, 1949–1955 (Box 293, Folder 3083-3084)
        - Shan-Kar and His Hindu Ballet, 1937 (Box 293, Folder 3085)
        - Slavenska Franklin Ballet, 1952 (Box 293, Folder 3086)
        - Slavenska Tihmar and Company, undated (Box 293, Folder 3087)
        - Ted Shawn and His Ensemble of Men Dancers, 1934, 1938 (Box 293, Folder 3088)
        - Vicente Escudero and His Ensemble, 1932 (Box 293, Folder 3089)
        - Miscellaneous handbills, brochures, etc., 1919–1965 (Box 293, Folder 3090)
      - Film, 1922–1964 (Box 294, Folder 3091-3093)
        Includes programs and/or flyers for Salome with Nazimova (1922); Thalia Summer Film Fesitval, New York (1952-1964); and the New York Film Festival (1963)
      - Music, 1902–1964 (Box 294, Folder 3094-3095)
      - Theater, 1917–1962 (Box 294, Folder 3096-3101)
        Includes programs and or/flyers for Broadway and off-Broadway performances; programs from performances of plays by Eugene O'Neill; and printed material relating to the Theatre Guild
      - Events
        - Capezio Dance Award, 1956–1964 (Box 294, Folder 3102)
        - American Theatre Wing First Night Ball, 1955 December 30 (Box 294, Folder 3103)
      - Miscellaneous arts groups solititations, 1952–1964 (Box 294, Folder 3104)
    - Art Gallery/Museum Exhibit Catalogs and Flyers
      Chiefly from New York galleries
      - A-B, 1939–1964 (Box 295, Folder 3105)
      - C-I, 1927–1962 (Box 295, Folder 3106)
      - J-L, 1932–1939 (Box 295, Folder 3107)
      - M, 1937–1964 (Box 295, Folder 3108)
      - N-P, 1914–1961 (Box 295, Folder 3109)
      - S-W, 1939–1957 (Box 295, Folder 3110)
      - Photographic exhibit catalogs, 1923–1956 (Box 295, Folder 3111)
    - Book Dealer Catalogs
      - A-C, 1929, undated (Box 296, Folder 3112)
      - D-G, 1947–1964 (Box 296, Folder 3113)
      - I-M, 1960-1962, undated (Box 296, Folder 3114)
      - N-Y, 1958-1963, undated (Box 296, Folder 3115)
    - Publishers' Catalogs and Flyers
      - Borzoi Books, 1937–1960 (Box 296, Folder 3116-3119)
      - A-C, 1962, undated (Box 297, Folder 3120)
      - D-G, 1933-1962, undated (Box 297, Folder 3121)
      - [Grossman Publishers], undated (Box 287, Folder 3048)
      - H-K, 1922-1963, undated (Box 297, Folder 3122)
      - L-O, 1921-1957, undated (Box 297, Folder 3123)
      - R-S, undated (Box 297, Folder 3124)
    - Book jackets (Box 297, Folder 3125)
      Includes jackets for Hardigut by Edna St. Vincent Millay (Boni & Liveright); Isak Dinesen A Memorial edited by Clara Svendsen (Random House); Jungle Saints by Philippa Schuyler (Herder); and More Stately Mansions by Eugene O'Neill (Yale)
    - Advertisements and Brochures
      - Clothing, 1918-1964, undated (Box 297, Folder 3126)
      - Food and drink, 1958-1965, undated (Box 297, Folder 3127)
      - Health and hygiene products, 1965, undated (Box 297, Folder 3128)
      - Housewares, 1947-1958, undated (Box 297, Folder 3129)
      - Photographic supplies, 1933-1972, undated (Box 297, Folder 3130-3131)
      - Sound recordings, 1951-1960, undated (Box 297, Folder 3132)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963, undated (Box 297, Folder 3133)
    - Posters and Broadsides
      - "Concert d'Oeuvres de Virgil Thomson", [no year] May 20 (Box 310 (Broadside oversize))
        Advertisement for concert at Nouvelle Salle d'Orgue du Conservatoire, Paris
      - "Concert d'Oeuvres de Jeunes Compositeurs Americains", 1929 June 17 (Box 308 (Broadside))
        Advertisement for concert at Salle Chopin, Paris, including works by Aaron Copeland and Virgil Thomson
      - Feldman/Brown concert, 1963 (Box 303 (Oversize), Folder 3173)
      - New York Public Library Dance Collection, undated (Box 303 (Oversize), Folder 3174)
        Solicitation for donors
      - "Playboy's Star Frolic", [1921] (Box 303 (Oversize), Folder 3175)
        Broadside advertising the costume ball at Playboy Club
      - "Tallulah Bankhead Engaged", undated (Box 309 (Broadside))
        Evening Standard newsstand poster
    - Clippings, circa 1920-1964
      - Art (Box 304, Folder 3177-3183)
      - Athletics (Box 304, Folder 3184)
      - Book reviews (Box 304, Folder 3185-3186)
      - Dance (Box 304, Folder 3187-3188)
      - Food (Box 304, Folder 3189)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 305, Folder 3190)
      - Music (Box 305, Folder 3191-3192)
      - Newspaper columns (Box 305, Folder 3193)
      - Photojournalism (Box 305, Folder 3194-3195)
      - Public figures (Box 305, Folder 3196-3198)
      - Social Issues (Box 306, Folder 3199)
      - Theater, Television and Film (Box 306, Folder 3200-3206)
      - Theater, Television and Film (Box 307, Folder 3207)
      - Writers (Box 307, Folder 3208-3212)
      - Charlotte Van Vechten, 1942 (Box 303 (Oversize), Folder 3176)
- Restricted Fragile, 7.01; 12 boxes
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files except for clippings relating to World War I and Edgar Saltus which were too fragile to be duplicated. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 1 (Box 313, Folder 3213)
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 313, Folder 3214)
  - Box 1, folder 6 (Box 313, Folder 3215)
  - Box 1, folder 7 (Box 313, Folder 3216)
  - Box 1, folder 8 (Box 313, Folder 3217)
  - Box 1, folder 9 (Box 313, Folder 3218)
  - Box 2, folder 10 (Box 313, Folder 3219)
  - Box 2, folder 16 (Box 313, Folder 3220)
  - Box 3, folder 27 (Box 313, Folder 3221)
  - Box 4, folder 41 (Box 313, Folder 3222)
  - Box 4, folder 45 (Box 313, Folder 3223)
  - Box 5, folder 53 (Box 313, Folder 3224)
  - Box 5, folder 54 (Box 313, Folder 3225)
  - Box 5, folder 59 (Box 313, Folder 3226)
  - Box 5, folder 63 (Box 313, Folder 3227)
  - Box 5, folder 64 (Box 313, Folder 3228)
  - Box 6, folder 65 (Box 313, Folder 3229)
  - Box 6, folder 66 (Box 313, Folder 3230)
  - Box 6, folder 68 (Box 313, Folder 3231)
  - Box 6, folder 69 (Box 313, Folder 3232)
  - Box 6, folder 70 (Box 313, Folder 3233)
  - Box 6, folder 71 (Box 313, Folder 3234)
  - Box 6, folder 72 (Box 313, Folder 3235)
  - Box 7, folder 81 (Box 313, Folder 3236)
  - Box 7, folder 83 (Box 313, Folder 3237)
  - Box 7, folder 84 (Box 313, Folder 3238)
  - Box 7, folder 89 (Box 313, Folder 3239)
  - Box 7, folder 90 (Box 313, Folder 3240)
  - Box 8, folder 92 (Box 313, Folder 3241)
  - Box 8, folder 93 (Box 313, Folder 3242)
  - Box 8, folder 97 (Box 313, Folder 3243)
  - Box 8, folder 98 (Box 313, Folder 3244)
  - Box 8, folder 99 (Box 313, Folder 3245)
  - Box 9, folder 101 (Box 313, Folder 3246)
  - Box 9, folder 102 (Box 313, Folder 3247)
  - Box 9, folder 103 (Box 313, Folder 3248)
  - Box 9, folder 104 (Box 313, Folder 3249)
  - Box 10, folder 112 (Box 313, Folder 3250)
  - Box 10, folder 113 (Box 313, Folder 3251)
  - Box 10, folder 116 (Box 313, Folder 3252)
  - Box 10, folder 117 (Box 313, Folder 3253)
  - Box 10, folder 118 (Box 313, Folder 3254)
  - Box 11, folder 125 (Box 313, Folder 3255)
  - Box 11, folder 127 (Box 313, Folder 3256)
  - Box 11, foler 128 (Box 313, Folder 3257)
  - Box 11, folder 129 (Box 313, Folder 3258)
  - Box 11, folder 130 (Box 313, Folder 3259)
  - Box 11, folder 132 (Box 313, Folder 3260)
  - Box 11, folder 133 (Box 313, Folder 3261)
  - Box 12, folder 134 (Box 313, Folder 3262)
  - Box 12, folder 135 (Box 313, Folder 3263)
  - Box 12, folder 137 (Box 313, Folder 3264)
  - Box 12, folder 139 (Box 313, Folder 3265)
  - Box 13, folder 143 (Box 313, Folder 3266)
  - Box 13, folder 148 (Box 313, Folder 3267)
  - Box 13, folder 149 (Box 313, Folder 3268)
  - Box 13, folder 150 (Box 313, Folder 3269)
  - Box 13, folder 157 (Box 313, Folder 3270)
  - Box 13, folder 158 (Box 313, Folder 3271)
  - Box 14, folder 169 (Box 313, Folder 3272)
  - Box 14, folder 170 (Box 313, Folder 3273)
  - Box 14, folder 172 (Box 313, Folder 3274)
  - Box 14, folder 176 (Box 313, Folder 3275)
  - Box 14, folder 178 (Box 313, Folder 3276)
  - Box 14, folder 179 (Box 313, Folder 3277)
  - Box 15, folder 180 (Box 313, Folder 3278)
  - Box 15, folder 181 (Box 313, Folder 3279)
  - Box 15, folder 184 (Box 313, Folder 3280)
  - Box 15, folder 185 (Box 313, Folder 3281)
  - Box 15, folder 188 (Box 313, Folder 3282)
  - Box 15, folder 189 (Box 313, Folder 3283)
  - Box 16, folder 195 (Box 313, Folder 3284)
  - Box 16, folder 198 (Box 313, Folder 3285)
  - Box 16, folder 208 (Box 313, Folder 3286)
  - Box 16, folder 209 (Box 313, Folder 3287)
  - Box 16, folder 211 (Box 313, Folder 3288)
  - Box 17, folder 216 (Box 313, Folder 3289)
  - Box 17, folder 219 (Box 313, Folder 3290)
  - Box 17, folder 222 (Box 313, Folder 3291)
  - Box 18, folder 225 (Box 313, Folder 3292)
  - Box 18, folder 226 (Box 313, Folder 3293)
  - Box 18, folder 227 (Box 313, Folder 3294)
  - Box 18, folder 231 (Box 313, Folder 3295)
  - Box 19, folder 235 (Box 313, Folder 3296)
  - Box 19, folder 236 (Box 313, Folder 3297)
  - Box 19, folder 240 (Box 313, Folder 3298)
  - Box 20, folder 246 (Box 313, Folder 3299)
  - Box 20, folder 247 (Box 313, Folder 3300)
  - Box 21, folder 252 (Box 313, Folder 3301)
  - Box 21, folder 261 (Box 313, Folder 3302)
  - Box 21, folder 263 (Box 313, Folder 3303)
  - Box 21, folder 265 (Box 313, Folder 3304)
  - Box 22, folder 273 (Box 313, Folder 3305)
  - Box 22, folder 279 (Box 313, Folder 3306)
  - Box 22, folder 282 (Box 313, Folder 3307)
  - Box 23, folder 285 (Box 314, Folder 3308)
  - Box 23, folder 288 (Box 314, Folder 3309)
  - Box 23, folder 289 (Box 314, Folder 3310)
  - Box 23, folder 290 (Box 314, Folder 3311)
  - Box 23, folder 294 (Box 314, Folder 3312)
  - Box 23, folder 295 (Box 314, Folder 3313)
  - Box 24, folder 296 (Box 314, Folder 3314)
  - Box 24, folder 297 (Box 314, Folder 3315)
  - Box 24, folder 300 (Box 314, Folder 3316)
  - Box 24, folder 301 (Box 314, Folder 3317)
  - Box 24, folder 306 (Box 314, Folder 3318)
  - Box 24, folder 309 (Box 314, Folder 3319)
  - Box 26, folder 310 (Box 314, Folder 3320)
  - Box 26, folder 322 (Box 314, Folder 3321)
  - Box 26, folder 327 (Box 314, Folder 3322)
  - Box 26, folder 331 (Box 314, Folder 3323)
  - Box 27, folder 341 (Box 314, Folder 3324)
  - Box 28, folder 345 (Box 314, Folder 3325)
  - Box 28, folder 351 (Box 314, Folder 3326)
  - Box 29, folder 362 (Box 314, Folder 3327)
  - Box 29, folder 368 (Box 314, Folder 3328)
  - Box 29, folder 370 (Box 314, Folder 3329)
  - Box 29, folder 373 (Box 314, Folder 3330)
  - Box 29, folder 374 (Box 314, Folder 3331)
  - Box 29, folder 375 (Box 314, Folder 3332)
  - Box 29, folder 376 (Box 314, Folder 3333)
  - Box 29, folder 377 (Box 314, Folder 3334)
  - Box 29, folder 378 (Box 314, Folder 3335)
  - Box 30, folder 381 (Box 314, Folder 3336)
  - Box 30, folder 382 (Box 314, Folder 3337)
  - Box 30, folder 383 (Box 314, Folder 3338)
  - Box 30, folder 384 (Box 314, Folder 3339)
  - Box 30, folder 385 (Box 314, Folder 3340)
  - Box 30, folder 386 (Box 314, Folder 3341)
  - Box 31, folder 392 (Box 314, Folder 3342)
  - Box 31, folder 407 (Box 314, Folder 3343)
  - Box 32, folder 417 (Box 314, Folder 3344)
  - Box 32, folder 420 (Box 314, Folder 3345)
  - Box 32, folder 433 (Box 314, Folder 3346)
  - Box 32, folder 436 (Box 314, Folder 3347)
  - Box 33, folder 438 (Box 314, Folder 3348)
  - Box 33, folder 441 (Box 314, Folder 3349)
  - Box 33, folder 443 (Box 314, Folder 3350)
  - Box 33, folder 444 (Box 314, Folder 3351)
  - Box 33, folder 448 (Box 314, Folder 3352)
  - Box 33, folder 450 (Box 314, Folder 3353)
  - Box 33, folder 453 (Box 314, Folder 3354)
  - Box 33, folder 455 (Box 314, Folder 3355)
  - Box 34, folder 462 (Box 314, Folder 3356)
  - Box 34, folder 463 (Box 314, Folder 3357)
  - Box 34, folder 467 (Box 314, Folder 3358)
  - Box 34, folder 471 (Box 314, Folder 3359)
  - Box 34, folder 474 (Box 314, Folder 3360)
  - Box 35, folder 479 (Box 314, Folder 3361)
  - Box 35, folder 483 (Box 314, Folder 3362)
  - Box 35, folder 484 (Box 314, Folder 3363)
  - Box 35, folder 485 (Box 314, Folder 3364)
  - Box 35, folder 486 (Box 314, Folder 3365)
  - Box 35, folder 487 (Box 314, Folder 3366)
  - Box 35, folder 488 (Box 314, Folder 3367)
  - Box 36, folder 490 (Box 314, Folder 3368)
  - Box 36, folder 492 (Box 314, Folder 3369)
  - Box 38, folder 508 (Box 314, Folder 3370)
  - Box 38, folder 509 (Box 314, Folder 3371)
  - Box 38, folder 512 (Box 314, Folder 3372)
  - Box 38, folder 513 (Box 314, Folder 3373)
  - Box 38, folder 518 (Box 314, Folder 3374)
  - Box 39, folder 521 (Box 314, Folder 3375)
  - Box 39, folder 522 (Box 314, Folder 3376)
  - Box 39, folder 523 (Box 314, Folder 3377)
  - Box 39, folder 527 (Box 314, Folder 3378)
  - Box 39, folder 529 (Box 314, Folder 3379)
  - Box 40, folder 531 (Box 314, Folder 3380)
  - Box 40, folder 532 (Box 314, Folder 3381)
  - Box 40, folder 533 (Box 314, Folder 3382)
  - Box 40, folder 534 (Box 314, Folder 3383)
  - Box 40, folder 535 (Box 314, Folder 3384)
  - Box 40, folder 537 (Box 314, Folder 3385)
  - Box 40, folder 538 (Box 314, Folder 3386)
  - Box 41, folder 540 (Box 314, Folder 3387)
  - Box 41, folder 543 (Box 314, Folder 3388)
  - Box 41, folder 544 (Box 314, Folder 3389)
  - Box 41, folder 548 (Box 314, Folder 3390)
  - Box 42, folder 556 (Box 314, Folder 3391)
  - Box 42, folder 557 (Box 314, Folder 3392)
  - Box 42, folder 561 (Box 314, Folder 3393)
  - Box 42, folder 562 (Box 314, Folder 3394)
  - Box 42, folder 565 (Box 314, Folder 3395)
  - Box 42, folder 572 (Box 314, Folder 3396)
  - Box 42, folder 580 (Box 314, Folder 3397)
  - Box 43, folder 581 (Box 314, Folder 3398)
  - Box 43, folder 589 (Box 314, Folder 3399)
  - Box 43, folder 590 (Box 314, Folder 3400)
  - Box 44, folder 593 (Box 314, Folder 3401)
  - Box 44, folder 597 (Box 314, Folder 3402)
  - Box 44, folder 598 (Box 314, Folder 3403)
  - Box 44, folder 601 (Box 314, Folder 3404)
  - Box 44, folder 604 (Box 314, Folder 3405)
  - Box 45, folder 606 (Box 314, Folder 3406)
  - Box 45, folder 607 (Box 314, Folder 3407)
  - Box 46, folder 618 (Box 314, Folder 3408)
  - Box 46, folder 620 (Box 314, Folder 3409)
  - Box 46, folder 624 (Box 314, Folder 3410)
  - Box 46, folder 625 (Box 314, Folder 3411)
  - Box 46, folder 626 (Box 314, Folder 3412)
  - Box 46, folder 629 (Box 314, Folder 3413)
  - Box 46, folder 631 (Box 314, Folder 3414)
  - Box 47, folder 635 (Box 314, Folder 3415)
  - Box 47, folder 636 (Box 314, Folder 3416)
  - Box 47, folder 637 (Box 314, Folder 3417)
  - Box 47, folder 638 (Box 314, Folder 3418)
  - Box 47, folder 645 (Box 314, Folder 3419)
  - Box 47, folder 646 (Box 314, Folder 3420)
  - Box 48, folder 648 (Box 315, Folder 3421)
  - Box 48, folder 649 (Box 315, Folder 3422)
  - Box 48, folder 654 (Box 315, Folder 3423)
  - Box 48, folder 655 (Box 315, Folder 3424)
  - Box 48, folder 658 (Box 315, Folder 3425)
  - Box 48, folder 660 (Box 315, Folder 3426)
  - Box 49, folder 661 (Box 315, Folder 3427)
  - Box 49, folder 667 (Box 315, Folder 3428)
  - Box 49, folder 668 (Box 315, Folder 3429)
  - Box 50, folder 676 (Box 315, Folder 3430)
  - Box 50, folder 677 (Box 315, Folder 3431)
  - Box 50, folder 679 (Box 315, Folder 3432)
  - Box 50, folder 683 (Box 315, Folder 3433)
  - Box 50, folder 687 (Box 315, Folder 3434)
  - Box 50, folder 690 (Box 315, Folder 3435)
  - Box 50, folder 691 (Box 315, Folder 3436)
  - Box 50, folder 692 (Box 315, Folder 3437)
  - Box 50, folder 693 (Box 315, Folder 3438)
  - Box 51, folder 700 (Box 315, Folder 3439)
  - Box 51, folder 704 (Box 315, Folder 3440)
  - Box 51, folder 709 (Box 315, Folder 3441)
  - Box 52, folder 710 (Box 315, Folder 3442)
  - Box 52, folder 711 (Box 315, Folder 3443)
  - Box 52, folder712 (Box 315, Folder 3444)
  - Box 52, folder 716 (Box 315, Folder 3445)
  - Box 52, folder 718 (Box 315, Folder 3446)
  - Box 52, folder 719 (Box 315, Folder 3447)
  - Box 52, folder 720 (Box 315, Folder 3448)
  - Box 52, folder 722 (Box 315, Folder 3449)
  - Box 52, folder 725 (Box 315, Folder 3450)
  - Box 53, folder 731 (Box 315, Folder 3451)
  - Box 53, folder 734 (Box 315, Folder 3452)
  - Box 53, folder 736 (Box 315, Folder 3453)
  - Box 53, folder 737 (Box 315, Folder 3454)
  - Box 53, folder 739 (Box 315, Folder 3455)
  - Box 53, folder 740 (Box 315, Folder 3456)
  - Box 53, folder 741 (Box 315, Folder 3457)
  - Box 54, folder 744 (Box 315, Folder 3458)
  - Box 54, folder 754 (Box 315, Folder 3459)
  - Box 54, folder 751 (Box 315, Folder 3460)
  - Box 54, folder 752 (Box 315, Folder 3461)
  - Box 54, folder 757 (Box 315, Folder 3462)
  - Box 54, folder 762 (Box 315, Folder 3463)
  - Box 54, folder 767 (Box 315, Folder 3464)
  - Box 55, folder 772 (Box 315, Folder 3465)
  - Box 55, folder 773 (Box 315, Folder 3466)
  - Box 55, folder 776 (Box 315, Folder 3467)
  - Box 55, folder 777 (Box 315, Folder 3468)
  - Box 55, folder 778 (Box 315, Folder 3469)
  - Box 55, folder 779 (Box 315, Folder 3470)
  - Box 55, folder 780 (Box 315, Folder 3471)
  - Box 55, folder 781 (Box 315, Folder 3472)
  - Box 55, folder 783 (Box 315, Folder 3473)
  - Box 55, folder 785 (Box 315, Folder 3474)
  - Box 56, folder 789 (Box 315, Folder 3475)
  - Box 56, folder 791 (Box 315, Folder 3476)
  - Box 56, folder 798 (Box 315, Folder 3477)
  - Box 56, folder 800 (Box 315, Folder 3478)
  - Box 56, folder 804 (Box 315, Folder 3479)
  - Box 56, folder 805 (Box 315, Folder 3480)
  - Box 57, folder 808 (Box 315, Folder 3481)
  - Box 57, folder 810 (Box 315, Folder 3482)
  - Box 57, folder 812 (Box 315, Folder 3483)
  - Box 57, folder 814 (Box 315, Folder 3484)
  - Box 57, folder 815 (Box 315, Folder 3485)
  - Box 57, folder 816 (Box 315, Folder 3486)
  - Box 58, folder 825 (Box 315, Folder 3487)
  - Box 58, folder 827 (Box 315, Folder 3488)
  - Box 59, folder 830 (Box 315, Folder 3489)
  - Box 59, folder 832 (Box 315, Folder 3490)
  - Box 59, folder 833 (Box 315, Folder 3491)
  - Box 59, folder 837 (Box 315, Folder 3492)
  - Box 59, folder 839 (Box 315, Folder 3493)
  - Box 60, folder 845 (Box 315, Folder 3494)
  - Box 60, folder 847 (Box 315, Folder 3495)
  - Box 60, folder 852 (Box 315, Folder 3496)
  - Box 61, folder 861 (Box 315, Folder 3497)
  - Box 61, folder 868 (Box 315, Folder 3498)
  - Box 61, folder 870 (Box 315, Folder 3499)
  - Box 62, folder 879 (Box 315, Folder 3500)
  - Box 62, folder 880 (Box 315, Folder 3501)
  - Box 62, folder 882 (Box 315, Folder 3502)
  - Box 62, folder 883 (Box 315, Folder 3503)
  - Box 62, folder 887 (Box 315, Folder 3504)
  - Box 62, folder 892 (Box 315, Folder 3505)
  - Box 62, folder 894 (Box 315, Folder 3506)
  - Box 62, folder 895 (Box 315, Folder 3507)
  - Box 63, folder 901 (Box 315, Folder 3508)
  - Box 63, folder 903 (Box 315, Folder 3509)
  - Box 63, folder 904 (Box 315, Folder 3510)
  - Box 63, folder 906 (Box 315, Folder 3511)
  - Box 63, folder 907 (Box 315, Folder 3512)
  - Box 63, folder 909 (Box 315, Folder 3513)
  - Box 64, folder 911 (Box 315, Folder 3514)
  - Box 64, folder 912 (Box 315, Folder 3515)
  - Box 64, folder 913 (Box 315, Folder 3516)
  - Box 64, folder 914 (Box 315, Folder 3517)
  - Box 64, folder 915 (Box 315, Folder 3518)
  - Box 64, folder 917 (Box 315, Folder 3519)
  - Box 64, folder 918 (Box 315, Folder 3520)
  - Box 65, folder 919 (Box 316, Folder 3521)
  - Box 65, folder 920 (Box 316, Folder 3522)
  - Box 65, folder 921 (Box 316, Folder 3523)
  - Box 60, folder 922 (Box 316, Folder 3524)
  - Box 65, folder 923 (Box 316, Folder 3525)
  - Box 65, folder 924 (Box 316, Folder 3526)
  - Box 65, folder 925 (Box 316, Folder 3527)
  - Box 65, folder 926 (Box 316, Folder 3528)
  - Box 66, folder 929 (Box 316, Folder 3529)
  - Box 66, folder 931 (Box 316, Folder 3530)
  - Box 66, folder 932 (Box 316, Folder 3531)
  - Box 66, folder 933 (Box 316, Folder 3532)
  - Box 66, folder 935 (Box 316, Folder 3533)
  - Box 67, folder 940 (Box 316, Folder 3534)
  - Box 67, folder 941 (Box 316, Folder 3535)
  - Box 67, folder 943 (Box 316, Folder 3536)
  - Box 67, folder 945 (Box 316, Folder 3537)
  - Box 67, folder 946 (Box 316, Folder 3538)
  - Box 67, folder 947 (Box 316, Folder 3539)
  - Box 67, folder 948 (Box 316, Folder 3540)